Guide to the International Brotherhood of Teamsters Newspapers and Journals collection 1956-2002 IBT0031
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, October 23, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 90)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, November 20, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 91)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, December 18, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 92)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, January 15, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 93)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, February 23, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 94)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, March 18, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 95)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, April 22, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 96)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, May 20, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 97)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, September 19, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 98)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, October 24, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 99)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, November 14, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 100)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, December 12, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 101)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, February 13, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 102)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, March 13, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 103)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, April 10, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 104)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, May 15, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 105)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, June 12, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 106)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, July 10, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 107)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, August 14, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 108)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, September 18, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 109)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, June 17, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 110)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, August 12, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 111)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, September 16, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 112)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, October 7, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 113)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, October 28, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 114)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, December 9, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 115)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, January 19, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 116)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, February 17, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 117)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, March 17, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 118)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, May 5, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 119)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, June 2, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 120)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, July 7, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 121)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, August 4, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 122)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, September 1, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 123)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, October 6, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 124)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, November 3, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 125)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, December 8, 1993 (Box 21, Folder 126)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, January 19, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 127)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, April 24, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 128)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, April 16, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 129)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, May 18, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 130)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, June 15, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 131)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, July 13, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 132)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, August 10, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 133)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, September 14, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 134)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, October 12, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 135)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, November 2, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 136)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, December 7, 1994 (Box 21, Folder 137)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, January 18, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 138)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, March 8, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 139)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, May 31, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 140)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, July 19, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 141)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, August 30, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 142)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, October 4, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 143)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, November 15, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 144)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, January 16, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 145)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, March 6, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 146)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, February 17, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 147)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, June 12, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 148)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, July 31, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 149)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, September 11, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 150)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, October 23, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 151)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, November 20, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 152)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, January 22, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 153)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, March 5, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 154)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, April 23, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 155)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, June 11, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 156)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, July 30, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 157)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, August 15, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 158)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, September 10, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 159)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, October 22, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 160)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, November 26, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 161)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, January 28, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 162)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, March 11, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 163)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, April 22, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 164)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, May 20, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 165)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, August 5, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 166)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, October 6, 1998 (Box 21, Folder 167)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, January 20, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 168)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, June 27, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 169)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, August 8, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 170)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, March 28, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 171)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, May 16, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 172)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, November 22, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 173)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, February 21, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 174)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, September 13, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 175)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, October 18, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 176)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, June 14, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 177)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, August 9, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 178)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, March 24, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 179)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, May 12, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 180)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, June 23, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 181)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, August 11, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 182)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, September 15, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 183)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, October 20, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 184)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, November 24, 1999 (Box 21, Folder 185)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, June 26, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 186)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, February 23, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 187)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, April 12, 2000 (Box 21, Folder 188)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, September 12, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 189)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, October 24, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 190)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, December 5, 2001 (Box 21, Folder 191)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, February 6, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 192)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, March 13, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 193)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, May 1, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 194)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, August 7, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 195)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, September 18, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 196)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, October 30, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 197)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, December 4, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 198)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, February 5, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 199)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, March 19, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 200)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, May 7, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 201)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, June 18, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 202)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, September 10, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 203)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, October 22, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 204)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, November 26, 2003 (Box 21, Folder 205)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, February 2, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 206)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, March 4, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 207)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, May 5, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 208)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, April 7, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 209)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, August 4, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 210)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, November 24, 2004 (Box 21, Folder 211)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, March 16, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 212)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, May 11, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 213)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, June 15, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 214)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, August 3, 2005 (Box 21, Folder 215)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, September 13, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 216)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, October 18, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 217)
- Joint Council No. 42 Southern California Teamster, November 22, 2006 (Box 21, Folder 218)
- Focus, 1973 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Local 20- Team and Wheel, 1958-1959 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Midwest Labor World, 1959-1960 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Northern California Teamster, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Rockford Labor News, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Teammsters Local 337 News, 1971 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Unity House Reporter, 1960 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Washington Teamster, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Wisconsin Teamster, 1959 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- The Team Driver's Journal Vol. 3 (cover only), 1903 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- The International Teamster Magazine, 1948-1957 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- The International Teamster Magazine, 1960 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- Hoffa News Article, 1961 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- The International Teamster Magazine, 1962 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- Teamster Magazine, Compulsory Arbitration, 1962-1964 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- Teamster Magazine, Compulsory Arbitration (Duplicate), 1962-1964 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- Eastern Conference of Teamsters, Repeal 146, 1963-1965 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- International Teamsters Magazine, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters Magazine, Vol. 1 No. 10, August 1904 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters Magazine, Vol. 1, No 12, October 1904 (Box 29)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters Magazine, Vol. 2, No. 10, August 1905 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- The Teamsters: Official Magazine of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Vol. 4, No. 8, June 1907 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- The Teamsters: Official Magazine of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Vol. 4, No. 10, August 1907 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- United Teamster of America Journal, 1908 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- Photocopy of United Teamsters of America Journal, 1908 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- The Teamsters: Official Magazine of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Vol. 5, No. 3, January 1908 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- The Teamsters: Official Magazine of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Vol. 5, No. 5, March 1908 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- The Teamsters: Official Magazine of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Vol. 5, No. 6, April 1908 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- The Teamsters: Official Magazine of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Vol. 5, No. 7, May 1908 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- The Teamsters: Official Magazine of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Vol. 5, No. 8, June 1908 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- The Teamsters: Official Magazine of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Vol. 5, No. 11, September 1908 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- The Teamsters: Official Magazine of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Vol. 6, No. 1, November 1908 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- The Teamsters: Official Magazine of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Vol. 6, No. 4, February 1909 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- Local 24 Report to the Membership from Officers, Vol. 1 No. 1 - Vol. 1 No. 6, 1957 - 1958 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Voter Registration for Fayette County Article: "Remember Freedom Village!", 1961 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Ray Schoessling Request for Midwest Teamster Volumes, March 24, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- The Teamster Retiree, Vol. 3, No. 3, 4, 5, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- The Teamster Retiree, Vol. 4, No. 1, 2, 5, 1982 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- The Teamster Retiree, Vol. 5, No. 2, 5, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- The Teamster Retiree, Vol. 6, No. 1,2,3,4, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- The Teamster Retiree, Vol. 7, No. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- The Teamster Retiree, Vol. 8, No. 1, March-April, 1986 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- The Teamster Retiree, Vol. 9, No. 2, 3, 4, 5, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- The Teamster Retiree, Vol. 10, No. 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 1988 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- The Teamster Retiree, Vol. 11, No. 1, 2, 3, 4, 1989 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- The Teamster Retiree, Vol. 12, No. 1, 2, 3, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- The Local Vocal, Local Union No. 639 No.5, May-June, 1978; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Teamsters 491 News, Vol. 14, No. 1, January - April 2003; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Newsreel Teamsters Local 399, January 2010; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Voice newsletter, Vol. XXI, No. 9 Teamsters Local 445, 2010; Series 1 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Feds Probe Contribution to Carey, Chicago Sun Times, March 19, 1997; IBT 0031 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Teamster Magazine: The Hoffa Legacy, 2022; IBT0031 (Box Shared Box 35, Folder 8)